http://www.stainless-uk.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Notice
Stainless UK Ltd understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of all of our customers and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law.1. Information About UsStainless UK Ltd is a limited company registered in England under company number 1981236.Newhall Road Works, Newhall Road, Sheffield S9 2QLVAT number: 438 9898 70Data Protection Officer: Timothy Wells. Email address: tim@stainless-uk.co.uk Telephone number: 0114 244 1333. Postal Address: Stainless UK Ltd, Newhall Road Works, Newhall Road, Sheffield S9 2QL2. What Does This Notice Cover?This Privacy Information explains how we use your personal data: how it is collected, how it is held, and how it is processed. It also explains your rights under the law relating to your personal data.3. What is Personal Data?Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) as ‘any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier’.Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.The personal data that we use is set out in Part 5, below4. What Are My Rights?Under the GDPR, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Notice should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 11.The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 10 will tell you how to do this.The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by us is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact us using the details in Part 11 to find out more.The right to be forgotten, i.e. the right to ask us to delete or otherwise dispose of any of your personal data that we have. Please contact us using the details in Part 11 to find out more.The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.The right to data portability. This means that you can ask us for a copy of your personal data held by us to re-use with another service or business in many cases.Rights relating to automated decision-making and profiling. Part 6 explains more about how we use your personal data, including automated decision-making and profiling.For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact us using the details provided in Part 11.Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.5. What Personal Data Do We Collect?We may collect some or all of the following personal data (this may vary according to your relationship with us):Name;Address;Email address;Telephone number;Business name;Job title;Profession;Payment information6. How Do You Use My Personal Data?Under the GDPR, we must always have a lawful basis for using personal data. This may be because the data is necessary for our performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to our use of your personal data, or because it is in our legitimate business interests to use it. Your personal data may be used for one of the following purposes:Providing and managing your account.Supplying our products and services to you. Your personal details are required in order for us to enter into a contract with you.Personalising and tailoring our products and services for you.Communicating with you. This may include responding to emails or calls from you.Supplying you with information by email and post that you have opted-in to (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time.With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your personal data for marketing purposes, which may include contacting you by email and telephone and text message and post with information, news, and offers on our products and services. You will not be sent any unlawful marketing or spam. We will always work to fully protect your rights and comply with our obligations under the GDPR and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, and you will always have the opportunity to opt-out.7. How Long Will You Keep My Personal Data?We will not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected.8. How and Where Do You Store or Transfer My Personal Data?We will only store your personal data in the UK. This means that it will be fully protected under the GDPR.The security of your personal data is essential to us, and to protect your data, we take a number of important measures, including the following:encrypting data9. Do You Share My Personal Data?We may sometimes contract with the following third parties to supply products and services to you on our behalf. These may include payment processing, delivery, and marketing. In some cases, those third parties may require access to some or all of your personal data that we hold.Mailing houses, for mailing out on behalf of customers from customers databases.If any of your personal data is required by a third party, as described above, we will take steps to ensure that your personal data is handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, our obligations, and the third party’s obligations under the law.We may sometimes contract with third parties (as described above) that are located outside of the European Economic Area (the “EEA” consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein). If any personal data is transferred to a third party outside of the EEA, we will take suitable steps in order to ensure that your personal data is treated just as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the GDPR, as explained above in Part 8.In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.10. How Can I Access My Personal Data?If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a “subject access request”.All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 11. To make this as easy as possible for you, a Subject Access Request Form is available for you to use. You do not have to use this form, but it is the easiest way to tell us everything we need to know to respond to your request as quickly as possible.There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’ (for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.We will respond to your subject access request within less than one month and, in any case, not more than one month of receiving it. Normally, we aim to provide a complete response, including a copy of your personal data within that time. In some cases, however, particularly if your request is more complex, more time may be required up to a maximum of three months from the date we receive your request. You will be kept fully informed of our progress.11. How Do I Contact You?To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following details (for the attention of Timothy Wells).Email address: tim@stainless-uk.co.ukTelephone number: 0114 244 1333Postal Address: Stainless UK Ltd, Newhall Road Works, Newhall Road, Sheffield S9 2QL12. Changes to this Privacy NoticeWe may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.Any changes will be made available on our web site..................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................................How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
For more information and to enquire about our products, call 0114 244 1333 or email us at
sales@stainless-uk.co.uk
© Copyright 2016
Company Registration No: 1981236
VAT No. 438 9898 70.
All Rights Reserved. Web design by Direct Computers & Steel Studios.
